

**ALVIN KARNADI** 

Makassar, Indonesia | 0895 801 552 360 | alvin.karnady@gmail.com August 2001 (22) | linkedin.com/in/alvin-karnady-764493263

#### **PROFILE**

A senior year student in computer science from Universitas Dipa Makassar, with a passion for web and mobile app development, design, and editing. With hands-on experience in technology projects and adaptability skills. Fast learning and still continue learn new tect about programming language and tools.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Universitas Dipa Makassar | 2020 – March 2024

B.S. in Computer Science | GPA: 3.67 (up to 7<sup>th</sup> semester)

# SMA Nasional Makassar | 2015 - 2018

Science Major

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Journey Event Planner & Orbit Event Organizer – Makassar, Indonesia

Event Coordinator (2018 - Present)

- Coordinated events from start to finish, ensuring smooth operation.
- Built strong relationships with clients to meet their event needs.
- Managed vendors to ensure every aspect of the event worked perfectly.

## PT. Telkom Regional VII - Makassar, Indonesia

Regional Operation Center Intern (Aug 2023 - Sep 2023)

- Developed a web application for employee leave requests using Laravel Framework.
- Updated and maintained accurate client data.

#### PT. Medianet Sukses Abadi – Makassar, Indonesia

IT Support Technician (Nov 2018 - Nov 2022)

• Installed cabling and maintained clients' computer systems, software, and networks.

## **SKILLS & TOOLS**

- SQL (MySQL)
- Languange (Basic (Php, Html, css, Javascript, Python))
- Framework (Laravel, Flutter, Android Studio, Bootstrap)
- Tools (VSCode, GitHub)

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Ms. Office (Word, Excel, Power Point)
- Prompt Al
- Detail orientation
- Adaptability
- Communication
- Problem solving

## **OTHERS**

Certificate : BNSP Junior Network Administrator, BNSP Creating 3D Animation Movement